Forrest "Bud" Harris Photographs, ca. 1950s-2007 AIS.2013.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Negatives, ca. 1950s-2000; I.
  - 35mm Negatives, ca. 1950s- 2000; 1.
    - 2004
      - Thrift Drug Classic, June 15, 2004 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Undated
      - Maria on Phone (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Maria at Typewriter (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Jenkin's Arcade: Photographs of Woman on a Porch (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Mat's Christmas (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Mat and Crane Building Bridge (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Nick Simcic: Track and Family (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Nick Simcic: Track (Box 1, Folder 8)
      - Nick Simcic: Computer (Box 1, Folder 9)
      - Parkway: Negative #12, Horizontal J&L Steel (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Paul (Box 1, Folder 13)
      - Paul and MM Halloween (Box 1, Folder 14)
      - Paul's Negatives (Box 1, Folder 15)
      - Paul and Kids: Good Portrait of Paul and Steven (Steven age 6) (Box 1, Folder 16)
      - Paul's Negatives and Kids (Box 1, Folder 17)
      - Penn Camera (Box 1, Folder 18-19)
      - People Inside a Mall (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
      - Pittsburgh Bridge and Iron Girder (Box 1, Folder 22)
      - Pitt Building: Forbes Field; Pitt Engineering Building; Mat and Sunglasses (Box 1, Folder 23)
      - Frick and Church Board (Box 1, Folder 25)
      - Frick: Oakland, Church Board (Box 1, Folder 26)
      - University of Pittsburgh from Carnegie Mellon University (Box 1, Folder 27)
      - Pitt Students; Joe Colangelo on Campus (Box 1, Folder 28)
      - Archadeck (Box 1, Folder 29)
      - Bud in Mirror; Maria; Cathedral of Learning (Box 1, Folder 30)
      - Brother Billy; Bill Evans (Box 1, Folder 31)
      - Forbes Street House (Box 1, Folder 38-39)
      - Julie Susser: Age One (Box 1, Folder 40)
      - Wooden Stadium Seats (Box 1, Folder 41)
      - "Somebody's Kids" (Box 1, Folder 42)
      - F and S and R, Alcoa Baltimore (Box 1, Folder 43)
      - Ron Rotham: Mustache (Box 1, Folder 44)
      - Namir: Bad (Box 1, Folder 48)
      - Men in an Office, Roll 1 (Business Week) (Box 1, Folder 49)
      - Business Week, Roll 2 (Box 1, Folder 50)
      - Man Sitting on Desk, Roll 3 (Business Week) (Box 1, Folder 51)
      - Portrait of a Man, Roll 4 (Business Week) (Box 1, Folder 52)
      - Men in Office, Roll 5 (Business Week) (Box 1, Folder 53)
      - Women's Health Services, (Business Week) (Box 1, Folder 54-58)
      - Blue Cross, Roll 2 (Box 1, Folder 59-65, 71)
      - Boston: Archway (Box 1, Folder 66)
      - Boston: Bikes, Harvard Runner (Box 1, Folder 67)
      - Boston: Dave Milton in New York, Bookcase (Box 1, Folder 68-69)
      - Boston: Mat Halloween, At Fireman's House (Box 1, Folder 70)
      - Bird and Sun; Charleston, South Carolina; Christmas Choir at Airport (Box 1, Folder 72)
      - Steel Gouye (Box 1, Folder 74)
      - MPE Program (Box 1, Folder 75-79)
      - Portrait of a Doctor (Box 1, Folder 81)
      - Jalbort as Doctor (Box 1, Folder 82)
      - Lois Muss (Box 1, Folder 83)
      - Larry Rosiek (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Lens Test: 90mm, Koppers Staff (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Little Girl: H. Milton Kids (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - Cathedral of Learning: Copy Negatives, roll 1 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Pitt Football; Art Reproductions, Copy Negatives, roll 2 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Pitt: Europe BOAC; Cathedral of Learning, Copy Negatives, roll 3 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Pitt: Computer Science, Cathedral of Learning, Copy Negatives, roll 4 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Cathedral of Learning, Copy Negatives, roll 5 (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - Cathedral of Learning, Art Reproductions, Copy Negatives, roll 6 (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - Cathedral of Learning, Copy Negatives, roll 7 (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - Pitt: Students, Cathedral of Learning, Copy Negatives, roll 8 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Pitt: Students, Cathedral of Learning, Copy Negatives, roll 9 (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - Portraits: University of Pittsburgh, Copy Negatives, roll 10 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - Cathedral of Learning, Copy Negatives, roll 11 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - Pitt: Cathedral of Learning, Copy Negatives, roll 12 (Box 2, Folder 17)
      - Pitt: Building Dedication Ceremony; Cathedral of Learning, Copy Negatives, roll 13 (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Pitt: Copy Negatives, roll 14 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - J&L Steel Mill: Cleveland (Box 2, Folder 20-21)
      - Judy Bank, Paul Pics (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Koppers: Sam and Hamburger, roll 4 (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Koppers: Metal Production, roll 1 (Box 2, Folder 36)
      - Koppers: Roll 2 (Box 2, Folder 37)
      - Koppers: Metal Products Baltimore, roll 3 (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - Koppers: Metal Products, roll 6 (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - Koppers: Wagon in Woods, rolls 7 (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Koppers: Good Metal Products, roll 8 (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Koppers: Farm, roll 9 (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Koppers: Fish Farms (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Kids at Tech Carnival; Bud and Alvin Inn; Mat at Kennywood; Pool Table; Leica in New York (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - Kaufmann's Department Store: Window Downtown, Night Shoppers (Box 2, Folder 45)
      - Railroad Downtown Bird, Ladies, Statue of Jesus, Kid and Steps Over West End and Point (Box 2, Folder 46)
      - Rita Silverman (Box 2, Folder 47)
      - Riverview Nursing Home (Box 2, Folder 48-49)
      - Riverview Nursing Home, Old Man with Banjo (Box 2, Folder 50-51)
      - Roland Kindhard (Box 2, Folder 52)
      - S. Eng (Box 2, Folder 53)
      - Roxie: Pool Room (Box 2, Folder 54)
      - Snow on Campus; Cathedral and Posvar House; Mellon University and Tree Sign (Box 2, Folder 55)
      - South Side Kids; On Blues and Dog and Fire Plug (Box 2, Folder 56)
      - Steelworker Face Close-up (Box 2, Folder 56)
      - Steelworker Walking Beams (Box 2, Folder 57)
      - Steve Sevients (Box 2, Folder 58)
      - Susson (Box 2, Folder 59-64)
      - Western Psych Play (Box 2, Folder 65-66)
      - 3 Rivers Arts Festival (Box 2, Folder 68)
      - City from the South Side, 28mm Rangefinder (Box 2, Folder 69)
      - Landman (Box 2, Folder 70-72)
      - Larry D'Arcy, Bud and Camera in the Mirror (Box 2, Folder 73)
      - Portrait, University of Pittsburgh (Box 2, Folder 74)
      - Drawings (Box 2, Folder 75-77)
      - Cathedral of Learning from the Roof of Carnegie (Box 2, Folder 78)
      - Law Retrieval (Box 2, Folder 79)
      - Pitt: Professors (Box 2, Folder 80)
      - Pitt: Computers (Box 2, Folder 81)
      - Pitt: Professor at Home (Box 2, Folder 82)
      - Pitt: Professor (Box 2, Folder 83)
      - Pitt: Model UN, International Meeting (Box 2, Folder 84)
      - Family at Home (Box 2, Folder 85)
      - Oakland Motel, Julie and Model (Box 2, Folder 86)
      - Pitt: Meeting in Nationality Room (Box 2, Folder 87)
      - Portrait of Man with Glasses (Box 2, Folder 88)
      - Banana (Box 3, Folder 1-3)
      - Baby and Strobe, Airplane Propeller (Box 3, Folder 4)
      - Parkway Clothesline, Cathedral of Learning (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - Armando in Office (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - 3 Catholic Boys and Father Jones; Posvar (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - Christ Guiser (Box 3, Folder 8-11)
      - City Hall (Box 3, Folder 12)
      - Chemical Plant (Box 3, Folder 13)
      - Charles "Cheech" Litman at the "Coin Exchange"; Grant Building (Box 3, Folder 14)
      - Maria, Mat and Susie (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Maria (Box 3, Folder 16)
      - Man and Iron Gate, Mat Age 1 in Stroller (Box 3, Folder 17)
      - Lisa Tamnes Colich (Box 3, Folder 18)
      - Pitt: PR Office Staff, roll 3 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Pitt: Panther Sculpture on Table (Box 3, Folder 20)
      - Portraits: Baby and Susie (Box 3, Folder 21)
      - Pregnant Maria (Box 3, Folder 22)
      - John Swergle: Arts and Crafts (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Joe Colangelo Family, roll 2 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Jet Delta Wing Plane (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - J&L Steel Lobby (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - Jackie Fine (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Happening at Stony Brook (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Girls at Church Ruins (Box 3, Folder 29-31)
      - Grandma, Maria and Kids (Box 3, Folder 32)
      - Girl in Park, roll 2 (Box 3, Folder 33)
      - Gateway Across Snowy Rail Road Tracks (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - Focus Test; Matthew and Hobby Horse 4 Years Old; Shadyside (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Fisheye Lens, Full Frame 17mm Pentax (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Eva Harris, Judy Ross, Jaquie Fine (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Paulina Porter (Box 3, Folder 37)
      - Condors Basketball Team (Box 3, Folder 38)
      - Cleveland, Ohio Stainless in Reheat Furnace (Box 3, Folder 39)
      - US Steel: Homestead Works (Box 3, Folder 42-45)
      - Mariachi Band/Shotguns (Box 3, Folder 46-54)
      - Jablonski (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - Librarians (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - Pitt: Classroom (Box 3, Folder 57)
      - Greenhouse (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - Professors in Lecture Hall (Box 3, Folder 59)
      - Pitt: Lecture (Box 3, Folder 60-61)
      - Pitt: Science Class (Box 3, Folder 62)
      - Couple Painting and Gardening (Box 3, Folder 63)
      - Pitt: Woman Teaching (Box 3, Folder 64)
      - Pitt: Couple Reading (Box 3, Folder 65)
      - Portraits of a Family, Man and Dog (Box 3, Folder 66)
      - Couple at Home with Baby (Box 3, Folder 67)
      - House on Fire (Box 3, Folder 68)
      - Men Reading Books (Box 3, Folder 69)
      - Pitt: Pharmacy (Box 3, Folder 70)
      - Women in Bookstore (Box 3, Folder 71)
      - People in Bookstore (Box 3, Folder 72)
      - Books (Box 3, Folder 73, 76)
      - Pitt: Scientists (Box 3, Folder 74)
      - Pitt: Professors (Box 3, Folder 75)
      - Pitt: Computer (Box 3, Folder 77)
      - Zebart Hearing (Box 4, Folder 72)
      - Job #: 26423 (Box 4, Folder 73-88)
      - Jones: Party (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Koppers: Doug Grymes, Machine and Tool Blue Books (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - 120mm Negatives, ca. 1950s-1999; 2.
    - ca. 1950s
      - PPG: 2, Girl in Fiberglass Boat, ca. 1950s (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - Women on a Playground, ca. 1950s/1960s (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Downtown Point, Old Bridges, ca. 1950s (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - ca. 1960s
      - UP-101: Alumni Wayfarers, Europe, Venice, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - UP-102: Alumni Wayfarers, Europe, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 53)
      - UP-103: Alumni Wayfarers, Europe, Russell Square, London, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 54)
      - UP-104: Alumni Wayfarers, On Plane, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 55)
      - UP-105: Alumni Wayfarers, Europe, Paris, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 56)
      - UP-106: Alumni Wayfarers, Europe, Plane, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 57)
      - UP-107: Alumni Wayfarers, Europe, Venice, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 58)
      - UP-108: Alumni Wayfarers, Europe, Paris, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 59)
      - UP-109: Alumni Wayfarers, Ambassador, Syndicat D'Initiative, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 60)
      - UP-110: Alumni Wayfarers, Europe, Bus, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 61)
      - UP-111: Alumni Wayfarers, Europe, Venice, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 62)
      - UP-112: Alumni Wayfarers, Europe, Paris, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 63)
      - UP-113: Alumni Wayfarers, Plane, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 64)
      - UP-114: Alumni Wayfarers, Plane, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 65)
      - UP-115: Alumni Wayfarers, "Tautro Cabulzi" Puppets, Amsterdam, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 66)
      - UP-116: Alumni Wayfarers, Baggage Check, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 67)
      - UP-123 A: Classroom, US Map, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 68)
      - UP-123 B: Korean Traditionally Dressed Women, Cathedral, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 69)
      - UP-123 C: Classroom, Korean Traditionally Dressed Women, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 70)
      - UP-131: Towers Lobby, Bookstore on Fifth, Cathedral of Learning, ca. 1960s (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - 1961
      - K.M.G East Ohio Gas, June 1961 (Box 7, Folder 1-12)
      - Donald Evans; Bud's Shadow, August 9, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - 1964
      - UP-1-3, 5-6: Professor with Bowtie, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 24-26, 28-29)
      - UP-4: Lecture, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - UP-7: Moby Dick; Nationality Room, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 30)
      - UP-8: Nationality Room, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 31)
      - UP-9: Lecture in Italian Nationality Room, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 32)
      - UP-10-11: Lecture in Nationality Room, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 33-34)
      - UP-12: Professor by Window, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 35)
      - UP-13: Algebra Lecture, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - UP-14: Towers Lobby, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - UP-15: Binary System, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - UP-16, 18-19: Algebra Lesson, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 39, 41-42)
      - UP-17: Algebra Lesson; Laws of Thought, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - UP-20: Towers Lobby, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - UP-21: Pitt Offices, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - UP-22: Professor, World Map in the Background, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 45)
      - UP-23: Skulls, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 46)
      - UP-24: Professor with Skulls, July 1964 (Box 7, Folder 47)
      - UP-122A: Homewood; Neighborhood Employment Center, August 12, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 48)
      - UP-122B: Homewood Elementary School, August 12, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 49)
      - UP-122C-D: Exterior of a House, August 12, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 50-51)
      - UP-122E: Children with Jump Rope, August 12, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 52)
      - UP-122F: Classroom, September 1964 (Box 7, Folder 53)
      - UP-125: Woman in Traditional Indian Dress, September 14, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 54)
      - UP-126: Man on Phone, November 30, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 55)
      - UP-127: Portrait of a Man and Woman, November 30, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 56)
      - UP-135: Esther Kitzes, December 18, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 57)
      - Larry Heller Wedding (Pitt Faculty Member), Roll B, December 21, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 59)
    - 1965
      - UP-138: Lecture, March 16, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 63)
      - UP-145: Street Scene, November 16, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 64)
      - UP-146A-H: Unidentified Researchers in Lab, November 19, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 65-72)
    - 1966
      - UP-147: Professor in Science Room, January 6, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 73)
    - 1968
      - City and Fireworks, 1968 (Box 48, Folder 24)
    - 1970
      - Parkway Construction: Uptown Looking Downtown, ca. 1970s (Box 1, Folder 11)
      - Parkway Construction: Two Workers Pull Beam, Downtown, ca. 1970s (Box 1, Folder 12)
      - Koppers: Pontiac Bumper, April 2, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 28-35)
      - Koppers: Southern Trip, October 5, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 36-45)
      - Gas Station, October 15, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 50-55)
      - Fayette Bank, November 1, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 62-65)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann; Shrink Wrap, December 28, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 70)
    - 1971
      - Koppers: Roofs, A, January 15, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Koppers: Roofs, B, January 15, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Steinberg House and Peter, February 21, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 53-56)
        See also job number 31871 (or, March 18, 1971).
      - The Balter House, February 25, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 59-63)
      - Marshall Homes, February 28, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 67-69)
      - Mat and Jeffrey in Darkroom, Superwide Test, April 17, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 82)
      - Koppers: Gazebo, May 17, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 1-4, 8-11)
      - Koppers: Meadows Stable, June 3, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 14-16, 18-20, 22-26, 28-31)
      - Feldman and Kahn, Mellon Strand, Construction Sites, June 8, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 36)
      - Koppers: Sandbox, July 12, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 55-61)
      - Koppers: Tar Roof, July 23, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 1-2, 5-9,)
      - Koppers: Harris, July 27, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 16-19)
      - Koppers: Wood Shed, July 27, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 20-27)
      - Koppers: Columbus Ohio; Gas Station Marathon Oil; House of Wolman; Lite Risers, August 3, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 29-34, 36, 38-39, 41-55, 57-60, 65-68)
      - Chatham Center, August 17, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 77-81)
      - Harris, September 7, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
      - Koppers: Dog House for Wolman, September 7, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
      - Koppers: New England, September 14, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 11, 14-16, 30-47)
      - Couple, September 26, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 49)
      - Levinson Steel, September 28, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 50-51)
      - Chatham Center, Feldman and Kahn, September 29, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 55-57)
      - TAC Air The Agency, October 1, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 59-62, 64-66, 68-70, 72-74)
      - TAC Air The Agency, October 1, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 4-15)
      - Koppers: Butler County, Special School, October 22, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 21, 24-29)
      - Koppers: Simpson Deck, October 25, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 30-34)
    - 1972
      - Koppers: Mobile Homes; Dayton, Ohio, January 19, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 4-6, 8-10, 12-14)
      - Wenman Schmidt; I.M.G.; Judy Fender Nurses, February 11, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - Koppers: Walter Wellborn High School, Anniston, Alabama, February 24, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 49-58)
      - Feldman and Kahn, R.P.C. Electronics, April 1, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 77, 82)
      - Koppers: Walman Foundation, Columbus, Ohio; AWUF Virginia Homes, April 4, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Toledo Laminated Beam, April 17, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 7, 9, 11, 13, 15, 17)
      - B.F. Goodrich, May 2, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 38-45)
      - Marglin: Computer School, May 24, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 52-66)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, 1901 Koppers Building Public Relations Department, July 28, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Koppers: Washington Plaza Pool, Sam Kauffmann, July 28, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 17-22, 24)
      - Koppers, August 22, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 36-45)
      - Koppers, September 25, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - 1973
      - Machines, January 11, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 15-16)
      - Koppers, January 16, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 20-24)
      - Koppers: Sam Kauffmann, February 1, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 27)
      - Petrolia Plant, February 1, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 28)
      - Computers, March 5, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 59-62)
      - Koppers, March 29, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 5-8)
      - Railroad Timbers, April 5, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 9-11)
      - Chickens and Old Car, May 7, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 43)
      - Old Car, May 8, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 45)
      - Koppers: Jim Pisarcik, May 11, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 49)
      - Koppers: Wrenton Coles Oven, May 11, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 50-56)
      - Baltimore Harbor, June 20, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 1-4)
      - Real Estate Family, June 26, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 6)
      - Koppers: Polos, July 19, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 31-32)
      - Koppers, August 15, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 39, 42, 44, 46, 48-51)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), August 15, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 45, 47)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, August 21, 1973 (Box 20, Folder 53, 55, 57, 59, 61, 63, 65, 67-69)
      - Feldman and Kahn, Joan Rozzo, September 5, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 11-14)
      - Koppers: Linn Noah, September 6, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 15-16, 20-21)
      - Wood, September 17, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 24-25)
      - Koppers, October 3, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 36-43)
      - Koppers, October 10, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 44-54)
      - Koppers: Wood Deck, October 19, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 55-62)
      - Koppers, October 29, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 1, 3, 5, 7, 9, 11)
      - Koppers, November 12, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 16-21)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, November 15, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 23, 25, 27-28)
      - Social Security Administration: Shoe Store, May 21, 1973 (Box 23, Folder 9-14)
    - 1974
      - Koppers, January 15, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 41, 43-45)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), January 15, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 42)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), January 22, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 54-74)
      - Feldman and Kahn, Stan Kent, February 4, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 78)
      - Ebo. L., February 8, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 79-82)
      - Koppers, March 4, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 83-84)
      - Sport Buildings, February 11, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 1-6)
      - Nuclear Plant and Fish, February 15, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 21-22, 25, 27, 29, 31-36)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), March 4, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 38-39)
      - Burson Marsteller, March 18, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 41)
      - Curt Miller, Burson Marsteller, March 18, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 44)
      - Koppers: Boonesboro, Kentucky, April 2, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 45, 47, 49)
      - Koppers: Light Poles, April 3, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 52, 54)
      - Koppers: Mercury Light Riser, Huck DeVenzio, April 3, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 55-56)
      - Koppers: VSFG Office, April 5, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 64-65)
      - Koppers: Environmental Systems (EEC Plant), Huck DeVenzio, April 5, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 68)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), May 8, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1-10)
      - Koppers, May 8, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 12-30)
      - Koppers: John Boal, May 21, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 44-49)
      - Koppers: Wood, May 24, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 50-57)
      - Koppers, June 7, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 58)
      - Koppers: Linn Noah, June 18, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 61-62)
      - Light Pole (Electric Pole), June 18, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 66-67)
      - Koppers, July 23, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 76-81)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), July 23, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 6-10)
      - Koppers, August 30, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 21-30)
      - Koppers: Light Pole, October 3, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 49-53)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), "Light Poles", October 3, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 55-58)
      - Koppers: John Boal, "Factory Scene", October 4, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 60-61)
      - Koppers, October 4, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 62-64)
      - Koppers, October 18, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 1-2)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), Steel Mill, St. Louis Projects, November 6, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 7-10)
      - Queens Park (New York), Dry Dock Restaurant, Inland Steel, Jersey Central Power and Lights, November 8, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 11-18)
      - Koppers, November 18, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 23-26)
    - 1975
      - Oxford Development Corporation, Monroeville Mall, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 28-29)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), "Florida", January 15, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 39-43)
      - Zoo, January 15, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 44-54)
      - Koppers: Unknown Stadium Construction, February 11, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 63-64)
      - Koppers: Gerald Wellner (Jerry Wellner), "Florida", February 24, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 73-78)
      - Koppers, February 24, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 79-81)
      - Koppers, February 24, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 83-91)
      - Robert Fletcher, March 30, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 8-9)
      - Koppers, March 31, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 10-12)
      - Building Materials, May 1, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 32-45)
      - Koppers: Linn Noah, Steak and Ale, Fireproof Plywood, Atlanta Georgia, May 17, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 51-57)
      - Koppers: Linn Noah, Chicago, June 5, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 61-73)
      - Koppers: Huck DeVenzio, Albany, June 9, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 74-77)
      - Koppers: Pool, June 9, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 79-80, 85)
      - Koppers: Water Plant, June 9, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 81-83)
      - Koppers: Totem Pole, June 9, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 84)
      - Boy Scouts, July 13, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Koppers, July 18, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 11-16)
      - Koppers: Decks, July 24, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 22-32)
      - Koppers, August 13, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 33, 37-39)
      - Construction, August 28, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 49-51)
      - Koppers: Helen Zimecki, J&L Steel Aliquippa, August 28, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 55-56)
      - Koppers, September 7, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 62-63)
      - Koppers: Bob O'Gara, Wood Things, September 7, 1975 (Box 29, Folder 65-66)
      - Koppers: Plant MGR AD with Firestand Wood, N.C.X., October 1, 1975 (Box 31, Folder 2, 4-11)